We, Seino!
Super Tough Strong Energy Positive Excitement Soul from Nagoya
I'm Yuzuki Ogura from Team Shaqi and
This is Michinoku no Stardust, Iginari Tohoku-san Daccha, and Rine Kitami.
Pleased to meet you.
So, purple talk!
Yes, sir.
I'm sure you're all getting used to it.
This time, too.
I'd like to share with you this time as well.
Aubre season and
and Kitami Line's
Special Talk Festival
Yes, I'm going to talk too much about one topic, so I've prepared a lot of questions for you.
I'm going to answer a lot of questions.
Here we go!
Jalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalala
What do you keep in mind when you perform at an event outside of your hometown?
If it's not our hometown, it would be festivals in Tokyo, wouldn't it?
I don't know...
But I feel like you're ready to do it.
It's like...
It's like a mela mela.
But Shaki-san is going in a different direction, too.
He's having fun and seems to have a lot of time on his hands.
No, I don't have a lot of time.
Yes, there is.
At the Stuff Run Plus...
Yes, yes.
Last year, we were all fired up, weren't we?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But they looked like they were having so much fun.
They looked like they were having so much fun.
So there's a way to be on fire like that.
Yes, it's burning, but it's not the same.
That's right.
It's a different way to burn.
Twak, you're kind of like, "Everyone's giving me a hard time.
That's right.
I have a strong image of a sudden burst of energy.
Yes, yes.
I think it's a wonderful, sparkling sense of youth.
Karen will be happy.
But you know... we're all kind of on fire.
We're all about having fun, so we do things like that.
I mean, we do a lot of that.
But at festivals and things like that, I think we're a little bit more like the Twak-chan type of melancholy.
That's right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We don't have much time to spare either.
You don't have time either.
Really?
We're desperate.
Really? Yeah.
Yeah, but I like the way we're doing it, with a sense of desperation.
That kind of idol image is my ideal, too.
I guess that's what makes it fun for me.
Then...
We're the same.
Common.
When you perform in Taiwanese events outside of your hometown?
What do you have to keep in mind?
What is it?
I've got it all together. I've been thinking about words.
What's that?
Melancholy.
Yeah.
Mela.
Mela, mela, mela.
Mela mela mela.
I'm gonna let you do your thing.
What is it?
She's changed.
We talked about that.
Did I change?
What's wrong?
It's burning.
Burning!
Words to keep in mind when performing in Taiwanese events outside of your hometown
Mela mela
Burning!
I've got it all together!
Thank goodness!
I'll play one more!
Please do!
When I perform a new song live for the first time, I'm thinking ________.
What I'm thinking about...
I do it with a rather smug look on my face.
We have a lot of meetings when we write new songs,
What kind of writers should we ask, what kind of lyrics should we use, and so on,
I'm very attached to the songs because of the meetings we have and the decisions we make.
I had a lot of things in my mind at the time of the first performance, and I was very particular about it,
I am confident that I can deliver it to you.
That's why we often do things with the feeling that they will be good enough for them.
We also depend on the music a little bit,
We tend to play songs that are rather boisterous.
So we often think about involving the audience.
We also decide ahead of time who is going to stir things up and who is going to stir things up.
I see. From the stage of the first performance, we are making the songs with a long-term perspective in mind.
I see.
I see. From the first performance, you were already ready to ride the bike.
Yes, yes, that's right.
That's right.
So you are conscious of that.
Yes, I am.
That's a different story. That's interesting.
If it was an autumn song.
Autumn music.
It makes me look forward to the future, because the first impact is important,
When the song comes, the dance is also rather powerful,
I think it's common for the dancers to be powerful when the song comes out, so I want the audience to think, "Oh, here comes another great song,
I think it's a bit like a festival when we perform in front of fans.
I understand.
That's right. It's about how much you can rub your feelings into the audience.
It's like the feeling you get when you perform for people you've just met for the first time, or when you perform for your fans, but you want to win their hearts again.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like a game. Like, "I'm going to win.
I have a strong feeling that I am going to win.
I guess you do, too, Tohoku-san?
Are you the same?
The same.
Yay!
Yay! Crowd!
Cover! I'm going to cover, cover, cover, cover.
I knew it, I knew it.
I know.
It's likely to be the song that leads the live performance from now on,
I think it's a good idea to do it.
Yes, that's right.
I appreciate it.
I think it will be, so that's what I'm going to do.
What do you think about when you perform a new song live for the first time?
The spirit of "I'm going to kick your ass!
I've got it all together.
I'm in the right frame of mind.
I think we're about to get burnt.
I don't know.
It's been quite a while since we started making it.
That's fine.
But I'm worried about the yuzuki.
It looks like it's only half cooked.
I wonder if it was really the other side.
It's fine.
It'll be fine. As long as you trust me.
Then, how is that side going, too?
I'm very nervous, though.
You all can look forward to it.
Our opponents so far are Yuzuki Komuro of Team Shirt and
Rion Kitami from Tohoku.
Bye bye.